{
    "subject": "resource/Viktor_Bolkhovitinov",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Aircraft_designers",
    "human_readable": "Viktor Bolkhovitinov is a subject of Category:Aircraft designers.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.926120936870575,
            "question": "Can you name some aircraft designed by Viktor Bolkhovitinov?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9228270649909973,
            "question": "What were some of the innovations introduced by Viktor Bolkhovitinov in aircraft design?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8745154738426208,
            "question": "How did Viktor Bolkhovitinov contribute to the development of aircraft design?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.873683750629425,
            "question": "Is there any information available about the impact of Viktor Bolkhovitinov's designs on aviation history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8688770532608032,
            "question": "What is the significance of Viktor Bolkhovitinov's work in aviation?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8479268550872803,
            "question": "Who is Viktor Bolkhovitinov?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8394628763198853,
            "question": "What category does Viktor Bolkhovitinov belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8380958437919617,
            "question": "What is the legacy of Viktor Bolkhovitinov in the field of aircraft design?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5308677554130554,
            "question": "What field is Viktor Bolkhovitinov known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44029712677001953,
            "question": "Were there any notable challenges faced by Viktor Bolkhovitinov during his career?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Viktor Bolkhovitinov is a subject of Category:Aircraft designers.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1150_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What field is Viktor Bolkhovitinov known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1150_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the legacy of Viktor Bolkhovitinov in the field of aircraft design?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1150_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What category does Viktor Bolkhovitinov belong to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1150_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1150_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1150_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1150_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1150_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1150_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1150_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1150_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1150_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1150_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1150_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide extensive information about Viktor Fedorovich Bolkhovitinov, describing him as an aircraft designer and engineer who made significant contributions to the Soviet aviation industry. Therefore, it is reasonable to conclude that he fits into the category of \"Aircraft designers.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}